by H.
Next notice
Cool, huh?
She's Honoka Akimoto of Nagoya's first idol group Team Shachi.
She's the hero of this video.
She's heading out for a swim.
Idol runway pressure today.
Thanks for watching.
Can you walk straight?
Do I wobble?
I've been everywhere today.
I'm going to make my appearance longer.
It's so dirty.
My breasts are so gross and dirty.
But you were told to walk smart.
You told me to walk smart.
Sure, I did.
So, walk quickly. What pose would you like?
You said, "Pose, you can show that character.
I wonder what that means.
I'm excited.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,  Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
I see the venue.
Where's first, second, first?
I don't know.
The second one is in the back.
This is the first.
Second.
Backstage.
Akimoto.Akimoto
Oh, there he is.
the most
Yay!
Where shall we sit?
Oh, my God.
Let's stay in the middle.
Around here.
Where shall we go?
Here.
My seat
Akimoto chose the lower chain.
Oh, maybe I can make it.
I can do this.
Really? Cassis is surprisingly good.
I don't feel Royal Jelly at all.
Are you tired?
I got it free with the New Days app.
You sit at the bottom of the table, and even if you drink a nutritional drink, you don't say you're tired.
I guess that's who Honoka Akimoto is.
We're going to rehearsal now, aren't we?
Rehearsal, right?
What pose shall we do?
I'll give you three poses.
How was your costume?
It's a very bright yellowish green.
It was so cute!
Akimoto's color in Team Shachi is red.
It's not a color she usually wears.It's a costume in a color she doesn't usually wear.
This is a bear posing with his fists as ears. I wonder if Akimoto will pose as a bear on this big stage.
And then the rehearsals began.
Idol Runway Collection is a girls' event for the new era that combines idol and fashion.
Unlike so-called "idol festivals", the main content of the event is a fashion show.
More than 10 idols will decorate the runway.
There is a rule about the flow of the idol runway collection.
After posing at the end of the stage, go to the right side of the screen.
If you pose on the right side of the stage, go to the opposite side of the screen.
The last step is to cross to the opposite side of the screen, so if you don't follow this route, you will cross over to the next person.
This path line is, shall we say, ironclad.
I think you should go there with a great smile on your face.
The posing part?
I'll do that part.
Everyone is pretty smooth mu.
Tea Farmer's pose was perfect.
He was the first farmer to show up.
Me too.
The biggest store on the runway was posing center stage
I didn't pose the bears at Miha
I wonder what kind of posing Akimoto will do in the show
Were you nervous?
I was worried I'd fall.
Am I looking dizzy now?
You looked like you could walk straight.
Really?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Walk straight.
I saw your costumes in the pictures.
I think the yellow-green one might be the loudest.Maybe a little yellow-green most gaudy.
That's right.
I wonder who it is.
I'm going to go do my hair and makeup.
You can choose any dressing you want.
I chose arrozel.
And curry
Beef stew
With summer vegetables.
With brown rice
Sushi
Fried food
Is.
It was crab cream croquette, wasn't it?
Oh, that's right.
That's nice.
Hey, Lanka.
Before you go any further...
You look like Lanka.
Oh,
What is it?
I had my make-up done.
How do you like it?
It's really nice.
The costume is yellowish green.
And the theme of the makeup?
I mean, there's a theme.
I heard there's a theme.
Like this.like this
Pearl type
And bangs are thin or up
And bangs are thin or up...
It seems there is a chapter on fashion.
Here it is.
Pearl
pink
It's like this...
Okay, then.
I'll take care of the rest.
Yes, I want to eat it.
Yes, ma'am.
Grandma and Mr. Ray, we'll have a drink.
It's good to start with a salad.
I want to eat.
I wonder what they start with.
Looks delicious.
Is it good?
It was lovely.
The catering was delicious.
We had a lovely tension that day.
You had dinner.
Drinks?
Dinner.
Dinner and drinks, this is a mishearing that doesn't match a single letter.
Yes, cheese.
How do you like it?What do you think?
Today's outfit is yellow-green.
I don't wear it often.
Well, I'm glad.
This green outfit
Akimoto didn't know yet
Akimoto didn't know yet.
What?
It's cute and shiny.
Go for it!
There's a green one I like.
There's a weird kid.
There's a weirdo.
He showed up with binoculars.
A member of the same group, Team Orca.
Yuzuki Daikoku.
That's Yuzuki Daikoku's scarf right there.
I went to see him and took his picture.
Oh, it was right around there.
Daikoku is a die-hard idol geek.
His binoculars to the island are not for show.
Your bangs were like cod.
That's right, it was a codfish.
That's how he went down there.
Like this?
It looks like it could go straight down.
That's cute.
Oh, my God, it's so lucky.
I'll be watching you.
Thank you. Thank you.Thank you.
Good luck.
I'll be watching you with this.
Bye. - Bye.
But, you know, I'm the third one, so I walk third.
You want to gulp?
I'll do the gapping.
I'll see them live.
Not through a screen, but through binoculars.
Daikoku taught me that's what it means to see them live.
Except for the hawks, the treguises, the kawaii voices and the actual equipment sounds of the whole world are quite strong with the colander!
It will be the ticking Clausival 2019 held this tournament!
Please open the wheelchair thrower's lid!
I don't know...
It's hard to tell!
one side
You also said you were going to drop one of them.
I don't know.
I don't know anymore.
Good luck.
You said it was the right thing to do.
I said...
Yes, I understand.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
please.
Please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please.Please.
This is also correct.
It starts here
It begins here
As we walk along
One of them fell off
Keep going
Just do it there
That's right, that's right, that's right.
You can wear it bare or not.
Akimoto seems to be once again realizing the depth of fashion on his skin
Making hearts with Akimoto is Mitsuki Hikari from the Tohoku region of Iginari.
Her catchphrase is rabbit angel magical girl.
You slept so well.
Oh, really?
Sorry.
Mr. Image is holding my little girl's head.
Oh, my God.
Rabbits sleep from 8 to 12 hours a day.
On average, they sleep eight and a half hours.
Pounding.
Singing alone again.
Hey, orca youtube
Hey, Hikaru, get on board!
Mr. Tork's
Let's get all your fans to watch!
I'm rooting for you.
Cute haircut!
I'm begging you!
Here, here, here.over and over
Here, here, here.
Okay, one pose.
Please.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
He's changed.
That's not good.
With your ears.
I'll be waiting.
Oh, no, no, no.
I just don't like it.
Hikaru Itsuki showed us the ear pose.
If we don't do this, the ears and the bear pose will be shown on the big stage
Are you nervous?
I'm not nervous yet.
Huh.
Go like this.
Go like this and go back.
Go back.
Yes, sir.
That's it.
Ten minutes to go.
Ten minutes before the show, Akimoto was reconfirming the line of flow on the runway.
I forgot it as soon as I left.
I was told to do it.
Serious
It's starting. Good luck.
I'll do my best.
Good luck.Good luck.
Bye.
Oh, it's 33:00.
I'm off.
And now it's time for the show!
Will Akimoto and his team be successful on this big stage?
Let's start with the Usagi Tenshi Magical Girl. Will she really do the ear posing?
Rabbit Angel Magical Girl is not posing as a rabbit,
She revealed the audience beautifully with her heart pose.
And finally, it was Akimoto's turn.
First, she had to look sultry.
She looked a little bashful, but she did a great job of making the right impression.
Next, the posing.
Please, just don't pose as a bear.
However,
Perhaps it was because I was dressed in green, but Akimoto was amazing.
She posed with her pinky finger raised in the air in a magical "magic sensory light killing" pose.
She also went in the opposite direction, even though she was supposed to go to the right.
The iron hand was easily shattered by the magic sensitized killing technique.
Finally, a mysterious shot was fired.
At this moment, a human intersection was born, something that would never happen on an idol runway.
A human intersection was born.
At this moment, a human intersection was born, something that should never have been created on an idol runway.
At this moment, a human intersection was born, which should never have been born on an idol runway.
At this moment, it should never have been born on an idol runway.
In this moment, it should never have been born on an idol runway.
This moment, never to be born on an idol runway.
This moment should never have been created on an idol runway.
And so Akimoto's idol runway came to an end, as fleeting and powerful as a cicada.
I changed my clothes.I changed my clothes.
I changed my clothes!
I'm in uniform.
I think these pearls are a little bit floating...
No, no, no.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
You're done.
Katsuran Way!
The girls were waving at me like crazy.
I wrote something about a van.
I wasn't going to do it in the first place.
But I gave her a bang.
She hit me with a bang.
That makes me happy.
A lot of people who live with me saw the show.
And they turned their penlights red.
I could see the presence of that many civilizations.
Thank you! I was so happy! It was very reassuring.
Someday as president.
I hope to perform that song or something.
Someday, I hope to be able to do that.
I was nervous.
Yes, I was nervous.
Your finger went that way, didn't it?
What? Which way is it? This way. You went this way.
Heh heh!
Well, let's have you walk down the runway.
I should have practiced like this.This is how I should have practiced.
This way!
Where did you do the actual bang?
They went this way.
Was it this way or that way?
I don't know. It was the third time we did it, and it was inside.
It was the third time.
This one?
Because I made a mistake.
I was like, "Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang!
I was already happy to be home.
I thought, "What? I thought I was going the wrong way.
I realized on the way back.
Yeah, it's a crossroads.
So...
Thank you very much.
I made a mistake.
Have a good day.
Bye.
I left it here.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Delicious.
It was interesting
what a surprise!
It's different from a live performance.
I felt like I had to do pretty much every single thing carefully.I felt like I had to do each one pretty carefully.
I thought that those who were good at what they were doing probably looked beautiful no matter when they were pulled out.
I thought they stopped firmly, but not too much.
Well, maybe it is important to stop firmly.
I thought about it afterwards.
After it was over. I learned something.
I learned a lot.
I was happy to be able to wear different clothes.
It was the first time for me to do my hair.
It was cute. Everyone was cute.
I usually only see them in idol costumes,
But when someone says I'm cute, it means I'm cute.
These events are fun.
Did you catch any new groups?
I hope the kids who were in the van will come.
Are you seeing any of the kids who got banged up?
Please come.
Ending